President, Office of the; Records ua000
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Office of the President Records
1827 - 2017 July 17
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
ua000
427 cubic ft.
83 captures
Administrative records from the Office of the President, which guides the overall direction and leadership of the school. This collection documents major university initiatives and trends since it's beginning in the 19th century.
Administrative History
The University at Albany, SUNY began as the State Normal School, a small public institution for instructing common school teachers, in 1844. In 1890, under the leadership of William A. Milne, the school became a complete institution of higher education called the State Normal College. At the end of Milne's term as president, the school evolved into the State College for Teachers, with a complete 4-year liberal arts curriculum. With the growth of the SUNY system under Governor Nelson Rockefeller, the school grew into a large public research university under President Evan R. Collins. By 1962 it was the State University of New York at Albany, with a complexly new suburban campus by the end of the decade.
Scope and Contents
Includes convocation material, 1879, 1922, 1934, 1948-1975; minutes of meetings of the trustees, 1921-1922, 1926; subject files, 1956-1978; and reports by presidential committees and task forces, 1973-1977. The presidents whose official administrative papers are held include Abram R. Brubacher, 1915-1939; John M. Sayles, 1939-1947; Milton G. Nelson (acting), 1947-1949; Evan R. Collins, 1949-1969; Allan A. Kuusisto (acting), 1969-1970; Louis T. Benezet, 1970-1975; Emmet B. Fields, 1975-1977; and Vincent O'Leary, 1977-1990; H. Patrick Swygert, 1990-1995; Karen R. Hitchcock, 1995-2004; Kermit L. Hall, 2005-2006; George M. Philip, 2007-2012.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is organized into 16 file series that reflect the original office files of the offices of different presidents. During the tenure of President Collins, the school evolved from a small liberal arts college to a large research university. It appears that duing that period, the president's records split into the personal files and official records series.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Web Archives
Acquisition Information
All items in this manuscript group were transferred to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives by the Office of the President.
Related Materials
Related collections in the M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives can be found in the subject guide for Criminal Justice and Prisons.
Access
Researchers may access this collection, yet often files must be reviewed by an archivist to ensure compliance with New York State Public Records laws. Please consult an archivist for more information.
College presidents--United States; Campus planning; College administrators; School reports; Public universities and colleges; Administrative records; Minutes (administrative records); Web Archives; Wages -- New York (State); State University of New York at Albany
- Early Presidents Records, 1827-1914; 1; 0.2 cubic ft.
  Arrangement
  Chronological by president's term
  Scope and Contents
  Contains personal correspondence of early presidents and formal annual reports 1912-1914.
  - George R. Perkins, personal correspondence, 1838-1849 (Box 1 (1-Early Presidents Records), Folder 1)
  - Joseph Alden, personal correspondence, ca. 1827-1885 (Box 1 (1-Early Presidents Records), Folder 2)
  - Edward P. Waterbury, personal correspondence, ca. 1880-1887 (Box 1 (1-Early Presidents Records), Folder 3)
  - Edward P. Waterbury, published materials, 1882-1889 (Box 1 (1-Early Presidents Records), Folder 4)
  - William J. Milne, personal correspondence, 1904 (Box 1 (1-Early Presidents Records), Folder 5)
  - Letter to William J. Milne from William Gibson, 1904 (Box 1 (1-Early Presidents Records), Folder 6)
  - William J. Milne, published materials, 1908-1914 (Box 1 (1-Early Presidents Records), Folder 7)
    - Memorial Exercises for Dr. William J. Milne, 1914 September 30
    - Letter to College Graduates, 1908 March 20
    - Memoria, ca. 1850
  - Report of the New York State Normal College, 1912 (Box 1 (1-Early Presidents Records), Folder 8)
  - Report of the New York State Normal College, 1913 (Box 1 (1-Early Presidents Records), Folder 9)
  - Annual Report of the New York State College for Teachers, 1914 (Box 1 (1-Early Presidents Records), Folder 10)
- Office of Abram Brubacher Records, 1904-1930; 2; 14.8 cubic ft.
  Chonological by year.
  Contains the correspondence and administrative records of Abram Brubacher, including speeches and publications.
  - Finances - Statistics, 1904-1938 (Box 1 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 1)
  - Auditor's Report, 1906 (Box 1 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 2)
  - Auditor's Report, 1908; 1922; 1930-1934 (Box 1 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 3)
  - Speeches, Addresses, 1908-1915 (Box 1 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 4)
  - War Records, 1908-1938 (Box 1 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 5)
  - Addresses etc. "Qualifications of High School Teachers", 1910 (Box 1 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 6)
  - Department of Public Instruction (Schenectady, NY), 1912; 1914; 1915 (Box 1 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 7)
  - Students who Dropped or Withdrew, 1912-1932 (Box 1 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 8)
  - Co-operations of Department to Secure Good Speech and Writing, 1914 (Box 1 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1914-1939 (Box 1 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 10)
  - Education and Social Service, 1915 (Box 1 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 11)
  - Inauguration, 1915; 1940 (Box 1 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 12)
  - Annual Reports, 1916 (Box 1 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 13)
  - President's Report of the New York State College for Teachers, 1916 (Box 1 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 14)
  - Speeches and Addresses, 1916-1917 (Box 1 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 15)
  - Annual Reports, 1917 (Box 1 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 16)
  - The J.K.M. Barry Controversy "The Menace to the New York State Educational System", 1917 (Box 1 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 17)
  - President's Report of the New York State College for Teachers, 1917-1918 (Box 1 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 18)
  - President's Report of the New York State College for Teachers, 1917-1919 (Box 1 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 19)
  - President's Report, 1917-1921 (Box 1 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 20)
  - Alphabetic File - Character Education, 1917; 1922-1924 (Box 1 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 21)
  - Annual Reports, 1918 (Box 1 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 22)
  - Association of American Colleges and Universities, 1918 (Box 1 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 23)
  - The Atlantic City Meeting, 1918 (Box 1 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 24)
  - Where High School Teachers are Made, 1918 (Box 1 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 25)
  - President's Report (Includes report on WWI services), 1918-1919 (Box 1 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 26)
  - Speeches and Addresses, 1918-1919 (Box 1 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 27)
  - Fairchild, Dr. Milton, 1918-1919; Undated (Box 2 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 1)
  - Addresses etc. "William McKinley", 1919 (Box 2 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 2)
  - Annual Reports, 1919 (Box 2 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 3)
  - Association of American Colleges and Universities, 1919 (Box 2 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 4)
  - Publication - "William McKinley", 1919 (Box 2 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 5)
  - President's Report of the New York State College for Teachers, 1919-1920 (Box 2 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 6)
  - World War I Memorials, 1919-1921 (Box 2 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 7)
  - Board of Visitors, 1919-1939 (Box 2 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 8)
  - Annual Reports, 1920 (Box 2 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 9)
  - Association of American Colleges and Universities, 1920 (Box 2 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 10)
  - National Conferences Committees, 1920 (Box 2 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 11)
  - Official Register, New York State College for Teacher, President's Report, 1920 (Box 2 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 12)
  - Student Registration, 1920 (Box 2 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 13)
  - Albany Burns Club, 1920-1921 (Box 2 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 14)
  - President's Report of the New York State College for Teachers, 1920-1921 (Box 2 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 15)
  - Vocational Guidard, 1920-1921 (Box 2 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 16)
  - Speeches and Addresses, 1920-1922 (Box 2 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 17)
  - Disarmament Conference, 1921 (Box 2 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 18)
  - Addresses etc. "The Teaching Personality Quotient", 1921 (Box 2 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 19)
  - Alumni Day, 1921 (Box 2 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 20)
  - Alumni Association, 1921 (Box 2 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 21)
  - Annual Reports, 1921 (Box 2 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 22)
  - President's Office - Applications Professional, 1921 (Box 2 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 23)
  - President's Office - Athletic Advisory bd, 1921 (Box 2 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 24)
  - President's Office - Coal, 1921 (Box 2 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 25)
  - President's Office - Commencement, 1921 (Box 2 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 26)
  - President's Office - Connes, Chanles v. Clark, 1921 (Box 2 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 27)
  - President's Office - Faculty, 1921 (Box 2 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 28)
  - Military Training Camp, 1921 (Box 2 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 29)
  - Myskania, 1921 (Box 2 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 30)
  - National Research Council, 1921 (Box 3 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 1)
  - NYS Civil Service commission - Personnel Bound, 1921 (Box 3 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 2)
  - NYS Teachers Association, 1921 (Box 3 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 3)
  - Publication - "The Librarian as Custodian of Tradition", 1921 (Box 3 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 4)
  - Publication - "The Teaching Personality Quotient", 1921 (Box 3 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 5)
  - Rural School Survey, 1921 (Box 3 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 6)
  - Salvation Army, 1921 (Box 3 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 7)
  - Summer Session, 1921 (Box 3 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 8)
  - Swift, Walker, 1921 (Box 3 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 9)
  - Teaching Personality, 1921 (Box 3 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 10)
  - Albany Girls Academy, 1921 (Box 3 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 11)
  - American Association of University Women, 1921 (Box 3 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 12)
  - Albany Girl Scouts, 1921-1922 (Box 3 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 13)
  - Alphabetic File - A - AL, 1921-1922 (Box 3 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 14)
  - Alphabetic File - Am- Ar, 1921-1922 (Box 3 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 15)
  - Alphabetic File - As- Ay, 1921-1922 (Box 3 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 16)
  - Alphabetic File - Baa - Bar, 1921-1922 (Box 3 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 17)
  - Alphabetic File - Bas - Baz, 1921-1922 (Box 3 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 18)
  - Alphabetic File - Be, 1921-1922 (Box 3 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 19)
  - Alphabetic File - Be-Bi, 1921-1922 (Box 3 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 20)
  - Alphabetic File - Bo, 1921-1922 (Box 3 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 21)
  - Alphabetic File - Bo - By, 1921-1922 (Box 3 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 22)
  - Alphabetic File - Bra - Bri, 1921-1922 (Box 3 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 23)
  - Alphabetic File - Bro - Bry, 1921-1922 (Box 3 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 24)
  - Alphabetic File - Bry - Bz, 1921-1922 (Box 3 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 25)
  - Alphabetic File - Ca, 1921-1922 (Box 4 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 1)
  - Alphabetic File - Ce - Cl, 1921-1922 (Box 4 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 2)
  - Alphabetic File - Coa- Con, 1921-1922 (Box 4 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 3)
  - Alphabetic File - Coo- Coz, 1921-1922 (Box 4 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 4)
  - Alphabetic File - Cr, 1921-1922 (Box 4 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 5)
  - Alphabetic File - Cu - Cy, 1921-1922 (Box 4 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 6)
  - Alphabetic File - D - Di, 1921-1922 (Box 4 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 7)
  - Alphabetic File - Di - Do, 1921-1922 (Box 4 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 8)
  - Alphabetic File - Dr - Dy, 1921-1922 (Box 4 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 9)
  - Alphabetic File - E, 1921-1922 (Box 4 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 10)
  - Alphabetic File - Fa - Fi, 1921-1922 (Box 4 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 11)
  - Alphabetic File - Fi - Fo, 1921-1922 (Box 4 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 12)
  - Alphabetic File - Fr - Fy, 1921-1922 (Box 4 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 13)
  - Alphabetic File - Ga - Ge, 1921-1922 (Box 4 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 14)
  - Alphabetic File - Gi -Go, 1921-1922 (Box 4 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 15)
  - Alphabetic File - Gr - Gy, 1921-1922 (Box 4 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 16)
  - Alphabetic File - Han - Hay, 1921-1922 (Box 4 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 17)
  - Alphabetic File - Har - Hay, 1921-1922 (Box 4 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 18)
  - Alphabetic File - He, 1921-1922 (Box 4 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 19)
  - Alphabetic File - Hi, 1921-1922 (Box 4 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 20)
  - Alphabetic File - Ho, 1921-1922 (Box 4 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 21)
  - Alphabetic File - Hu - Hy, 1921-1922 (Box 4 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 22)
  - Alphabetic File - I, 1921-1922 (Box 5 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 1)
  - Alphabetic File - J, 1921-1922 (Box 5 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 2)
  - Alphabetic File - Ka - Ke, 1921-1922 (Box 5 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 3)
  - Alphabetic File - Ki - Ko, 1921-1922 (Box 5 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 4)
  - Alphabetic File - Kr - Ky, 1921-1922 (Box 5 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 5)
  - Alphabetic File - La, 1921-1922 (Box 5 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 6)
  - Alphabetic File - Le, 1921-1922 (Box 5 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 7)
  - Alphabetic File - Li - Ly, 1921-1922 (Box 5 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 8)
  - Alphabetic File - Ma, 1921-1922 (Box 5 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 9)
  - Alphabetic File - Mce - Mck, 1921-1922 (Box 5 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 10)
  - Alphabetic File - Mcl - Mcz, 1921-1922 (Box 5 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 11)
  - Alphabetic File - Me - Mi, 1921-1922 (Box 5 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 12)
  - Alphabetic File - My, 1921-1922 (Box 5 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 13)
  - Alphabetic File - N, 1921-1922 (Box 5 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 14)
  - Alphabetic File - O, 1921-1922 (Box 5 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 15)
  - Alphabetic File - P, 1921-1922 (Box 5 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 16)
  - Alphabetic File - Q, 1921-1922 (Box 5 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 17)
  - Alphabetic File - R, 1921-1922 (Box 5 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 18)
  - Alphabetic File - Sa - St, 1921-1922 (Box 5 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 19)
  - Alphabetic File - Sta - Ste, 1921-1922 (Box 5 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 20)
  - Alphabetic File - St - Sz, 1921-1922 (Box 5 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 21)
  - Alphabetic File - Ta - Ti, 1921-1922 (Box 5 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 22)
  - Alphabetic File - To - Tz, 1921-1922 (Box 5 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 23)
  - Alphabetic File - V, 1921-1922 (Box 5 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 24)
  - Alphabetic File - Wa, 1921-1922 (Box 5 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 25)
  - Alphabetic File - We, 1921-1922 (Box 5 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 26)
  - Alphabetic File - Wh, 1921-1922 (Box 5 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 27)
  - Alphabetic File - Wia - Wil, 1921-1922 (Box 5 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 28)
  - Alphabetic File - Wo - Wy, 1921-1922 (Box 5 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 29)
  - Alphabetic File - Y, 1921-1922 (Box 5 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 30)
  - Alphabetic File - Z, 1921-1922 (Box 5 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 31)
  - Association of American Colleges and Universities, 1921-1922 (Box 5 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 32)
  - Budget File, 1921-1922 (Box 5 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 33)
  - President's Office - Budget, 1921-1922 (Box 5 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 34)
  - President's Office - Bureau of Education, 1921-1922 (Box 5 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 35)
  - Catalog Request, 1921-1922 (Box 5 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 36)
  - Catalog Request, 1921-1922 (Box 5 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 37)
  - Catalog Request, 1921-1922 (Box 5 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 38)
  - Correspondence S - T, 1921-1922 (Box 6 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 1)
  - Dormitory, 1921-1922 (Box 6 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 2)
  - Editorials, 1921-1922 (Box 6 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 3)
  - Faculty Council, 1921-1922 (Box 6 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 4)
  - Hurst, A.S. - Dean Syracuse University, 1921-1922 (Box 6 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 5)
  - International Education, 1921-1922 (Box 6 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 6)
  - Ar - Normal Schools, 1921-1922 (Box 6 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 7)
  - Pensions, 1921-1922 (Box 6 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 8)
  - President's Report of the New York State College for Teachers, 1921-1922 (Box 6 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 9)
  - Private File, 1921-1922 (Box 6 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 10)
  - State Architect, 1921-1922 (Box 6 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 11)
  - State Teacher Ass'n, 1921-1922 (Box 6 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 12)
  - Trustees File, 1921-1922 (Box 6 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 13)
  - Trustees File, 1921-1922 (Box 6 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 14)
  - AR - Phi Beta Kappa - Subject File, 1921-1923 (Box 6 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 15)
  - NEA (National Education Association), 1921-1938 (Box 6 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 16)
  - Writings + Publications - Miscellaneous Authors, 1921 (Box 6 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 17)
  - American Council of Education, 1922 (Box 6 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 18)
  - Annual Reports, 1922 (Box 6 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 19)
  - Horner, H.H. - Dean, 1922 (Box 6 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 20)
  - Inquiries Regarding Sabbatical Years, 1922 (Box 6 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 21)
  - Ar - Near East Relief, 1922 (Box 6 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 22)
  - Alphabetic File - Ka- Ke, 1922-1923 (Box 7 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 1)
  - Alphabetic File - Ki - Ko, 1922-1923 (Box 7 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 2)
  - Alphabetic File - Kr - Ky, 1922-1923 (Box 7 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 3)
  - Alphabetic File - La, 1922-1923 (Box 7 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 4)
  - Alphabetic File - Le, 1922-1923 (Box 7 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 5)
  - Alphabetic File - Li - Ly, 1922-1923 (Box 7 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 6)
  - Alphabetic File - Mca - Mcd, 1922-1923 (Box 7 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 7)
  - Alphabetic File - Mcf - Mck, 1922-1923 (Box 7 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 8)
  - Alphabetic File - Mcl - Mcz, 1922-1923 (Box 7 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 9)
  - Alphabetic File - Ma, 1922-1923 (Box 7 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 10)
  - Alphabetic File - Me - Mi, 1922-1923 (Box 7 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 11)
  - Alphabetic File - Mo - My, 1922-1923 (Box 7 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 12)
  - Alphabetic File - N - O, 1922-1923 (Box 7 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 13)
  - Alphabetic File - Pa - Pe, 1922-1923 (Box 7 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 14)
  - Alphabetic File - Pi - Po, 1922-1923 (Box 7 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 15)
  - Alphabetic File - Pr - Py, 1922-1923 (Box 7 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 16)
  - Alphabetic File - Q, 1922-1923 (Box 7 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 17)
  - Alphabetic File - Ra - Rh, 1922-1923 (Box 7 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 18)
  - Alphabetic File - Ri - Rod, 1922-1923 (Box 7 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 19)
  - Alphabetic File - Ro, 1922-1923 (Box 7 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 20)
  - Alphabetic File - Sa - Sca, 1922-1923 (Box 7 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 21)
  - Alphabetic File - Sch - Scy, 1922-1923 (Box 7 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 22)
  - Alphabetic File - Se - Sh, 1922-1923 (Box 7 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 23)
  - Alphabetic File - She - Shy, 1922-1923 (Box 7 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 24)
  - Alphabetic File - Si - Smi, 1922-1923 (Box 7 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 25)
  - Alphabetic File - So - Sq, 1922-1923 (Box 7 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 26)
  - Alphabetic File - St, 1922-1923 (Box 7 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 27)
  - Alphabetic File - Sti - Sty, 1922-1923 (Box 7 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 28)
  - Alphabetic File - Su - Sy, 1922-1923 (Box 7 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 29)
  - Alphabetic File - T, 1922-1923 (Box 7 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 30)
  - Alphabetic File - T, 1922-1923 (Box 7 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 31)
  - Alphabetic File - V, 1922-1923 (Box 7 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 32)